Attention, class. Attention.
Okay.
Hello, esteemed class of Furbish 6,350.
Make no joke. This language is no easy endeavor.
The vile Furby creature speaks to tongue of the devil.
And if you wish to live, listen to my word.
The self-centered Furbis love talking about themselves.
Where our first person pronouns are me, myself, and I.
The Furbis only know one word, Kah.
The greed knows no end to them. Money is Moo-lah.
They reject all civility.
Their No or Stop is Boo.
Before this class ends, I will leave you all with three key phrases.
I'm very happy is Kah mee-mee noo-loo.
You what? is Oo-nye doo?
And lastly, I'm not healthy is Kah boo koo-doh.
Thank you.